<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PUBG League</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="deposit_rules">Rules : \n
    1.Minimum amount to deposit is ₹10.\n
    2.Do not fake/spam any information.\n
    4.Deposited amount will be added to wallet within 12hrs.\n
    3.You can contact us in mail for any queries.\n\n
         If in case you spam any information your account will be removed
        without your intimation and your earnings will be cancelled.
    </string>

    <!--a99bb734-cbdd-4a72-bbe8-815b74c7554d-->

    <string name="withdraw_rules">Rules : \n
    1.Minimum amount to withdraw is ₹10.\n
    2.Requested amount will be withdrawed within 12hrs to your PayTm number.\n
    3.You can contact us in mail for any queries.
    </string>

    <string name="game_rules"> \n
        1. Please note that the listed entry fee is per individual and not
        the squad/duo team.\n\n

        2. Each member of a team (Squad or Duo) has to pay the entry
        fee and register individually for the match or tournament.\n\n

        3. If in anyway you fail to join the room by the match start time
        then we are not responsible for it. Refund in such cases will not be
        processed. So make sure to join on time.\n\n

        4. Do not share the Room ID and Password with anyone who has
        not joined the match. If you are found doing so, your account may
        get terminated and all the winnings will be lost.\n\n

        5. Griefing and Teaming is against the game rules. Any participant
        found doing so will be disqualified and their prizes will be lost.\n\n

        7. Room ID and Password will be shared in the app before 15
        minutes of match start time.\n\n

        8. Match will start after 15 minutes of Sharing Room ID and
        Password.\n\n

        9. Make sure to grab ID and Password before the Match Start
        Time.\n\n

        10. Make sure you join the Match Room ASAP, before the match
        starts.\n\n

        11. This match is Paid match. To participate, you have to pay the
        entry fee amount. There are total 100 spots available. Join it
        before all the spots are filled.\n\n


        12. Once you join the match custom room, do not keep changing
        your position. If you do so, you may get kicked from the room.\n\n

        13. Spots are given on the First Come First Basis.\n\n

        14. Last standing man gets the Chicken Dinner Award.\n\n

        15. You will be also rewarded for each kill. Check the rewards
        details above.\n\n

        16. Use only Mobile Device to Join Match. Do not use any Hacks
        or Emulators.\n\n

        17. If anyone found violating these rules then immediate action
        will be taken and respective accounts may get banned and
        rewards may be abandoned.\n\n

        18. If you have any queries then contact us on
        www.pubgleague@gmail.com.\n\n
    </string>
</resources>
